They always ignored us until we
became
impossible to ignore.
What do you think is a
desirable scenario for Benny Spoons in 10 years?
So, there's this AI thing going on here
that makes everything much more
difficult.  10 years is an absolutely impossible time frame, given
what we are seeing
.  I'm pretty
confident that our strategy can
continue to work and give us
a lot of satisfaction, but I think that
compared to what we do, compared
to our model and so on, there's
the possibility of being much more
impactful, much more
inspirational. We'll impact the lives of
many more people and we'll be an increasingly important
example, in short, even for others who
want to try their hand at
entrepreneurship, hopefully from Italy or
Europe. In short, there's a great
need for people like this.  M.